<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Terra Nullius</title>
    <link>https://trantor.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Terra Nullius</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 10:09:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://trantor.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Words and Quantities</title>
      <link>https://trantor.github.io/posts/words-and-quantities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 10:09:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trantor.github.io/posts/words-and-quantities/</guid>
      <description>Caveat lector As an Italian immersed in an English-dominated («English» here referring to the language, not the country) information environment, both the worldwide web AND its non-digital counterparts, I am often confronted with the pitfalls of information flowing or pouring from English-language sources into other-language domains through the often-discounted process of translation.
Apart from the cultural underpinnings and assumptions of the content produced by native speakers which are conveyed along with it and the sometime bizarre wording of non-native ones, there is one specific aspect which sits at the crossroads between language-specific semantics and technical terminology which I find to be profoundly irksome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A beginning</title>
      <link>https://trantor.github.io/posts/a-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 20:09:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trantor.github.io/posts/a-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Essence These few lines represent the beginning of an expression conveyed through the written word. Or perhaps the typed word.
I have been actively using the internet for more than 20 years now and first envisioned putting thoughts of mine in a public space at least 15 years ago.
That intent never transitioned from potential into actual, until now.
Hopefully now my thoughts and humble investigations into reality will prove of use to others and, let&amp;rsquo;s hope, to myself as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
